Excel File Analysis - Redacted Content
==================================================

Sheet: Sheet1
Employee Full Name | Employee ID | Date of In-Person Verification | Verified By (RA Name) | RA Signature / Initials | Authorized By (Supervisor) | Supervisor Email | Date of Authorization | Token Serial Number | Token Issuance Date
<PERSON> | EMP93203 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AL | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90386-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP32537 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | SG | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91521-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP99952 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AC | Micheal <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91367-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP89956 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | DM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97226-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Dawn Wong | EMP95067 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96190-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP55065 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <LOCATION> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95865-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP36328 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AK | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98976-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP71600 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | TM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-94852-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP53733 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RC | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93290-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP83247 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | DB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92160-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP95081 | <DATE_TIME> | Mrs. <PERSON> | MTT | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95215-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP61218 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AD | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91017-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP33145 | <DATE_TIME> | Allison Washington | AW | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90967-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP94400 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | BL | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99247-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP89626 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | <LOCATION> | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP65654 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | DL | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97695-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Nicholas Morris | EMP12431 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | WE | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95389-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | DS | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97232-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP10345 | <DATE_TIME> | Tiffany Washington | TW | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97928-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP18988 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | SH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93892-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> <LOCATION> | EMP73399 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JG | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90189-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP93948 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91341-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP66905 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90041-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP30696 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | WC | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98324-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP99106 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | VS | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99344-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP47454 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <LOCATION> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90191-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP88162 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-94556-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Morgan Williams | EMP82226 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JG | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | <LOCATION>-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP93437 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | TB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98856-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | <NRP> | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JS | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99200-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP72447 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | MB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91618-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP91574 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | VV | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99977-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Mr. <PERSON> | EMP19217 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | PA | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91961-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP80490 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | WJ | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99258-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP43226 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91982-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP44462 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | DB | Mrs. <PERSON> <LOCATION> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92635-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP18054 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | ES | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97270-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP44475 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <LOCATION> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93754-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP51381 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98697-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | <NRP> | <DATE_TIME> | Megan Hall | MH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96853-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP62118 | <DATE_TIME> | <LOCATION> | <NRP> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91530-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP37149 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RL | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95581-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP60881 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | DD | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96551-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP15282 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99984-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP17233 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92287-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP57691 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99842-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP11717 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JS | Morgan Gardner | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91507-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP59501 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93293-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP16269 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | PB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91919-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP95124 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92481-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | <NRP> | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | CC | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95085-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP90997 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | SF | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95544-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP57989 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93743-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP69903 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AS | Cynthia Cross | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-99641-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP64366 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | MS | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91882-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP91924 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | MB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90234-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP18861 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | SA | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91355-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP55759 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RS | <PERSON> <LOCATION> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97172-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP72039 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | TP | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96130-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP64890 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <LOCATION> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92756-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP98021 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <LOCATION> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91767-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP20027 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | BP | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96723-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP68293 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | MW | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97784-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Jared Wood | EMP25756 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AT | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97483-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP99658 | <DATE_TIME> | Mr. <PERSON> | MDM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90317-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP33809 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AW | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92709-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Shannon Herrera | EMP16694 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AB | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96307-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP17950 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | LW | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91647-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | <DATE_TIME> | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | KM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | <LOCATION> | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP52935 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RS | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96904-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP53163 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | SH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98928-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP38577 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> <LOCATION> | CCM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90154-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP90273 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AD | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95352-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP55818 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96504-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP45310 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | KM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96376-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP70154 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AF | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96764-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP85969 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <LOCATION> | Wendy Hill | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95573-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP56925 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JHD | Mr. <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98006-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP89170 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | EH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-97055-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP17676 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | MH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96430-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP51925 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | PM | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93097-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP41889 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RP | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91154-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP28360 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JA | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98908-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP37892 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | JR | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98894-AL | <DATE_TIME>
Mr. <PERSON> | EMP73769 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | KR | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93454-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP32363 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | MR | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-94466-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP28881 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | KT | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93080-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP55143 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AR | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90480-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP80290 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-90684-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP92129 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | CH | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96414-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP59421 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | RB | <LOCATION> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96755-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP25154 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | BC | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-93235-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | <NRP> | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | CR | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98976-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP99618 | <DATE_TIME> | <LOCATION> | CL | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96207-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP83172 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | CS | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-91650-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP18659 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AW | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-96166-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP25949 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | KM | Mr. <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98039-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP73321 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | AR | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-98039-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP13317 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | TS | <DATE_TIME> <NRP> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-95926-AL | <DATE_TIME>
<PERSON> | EMP14887 | <DATE_TIME> | <PERSON> | SI | <PERSON> | <EMAIL_ADDRESS> | <DATE_TIME> | HT-92897-AL | <DATE_TIME>
